Doesn't involve other associated funds of Gu Group
If more are added later
the associated company's fund usage
must be re-approved
with the guarantor's written consent
Otherwise I won't sign
Relax Mingyao
It's just phase one
You won't take on extra risks
Mr Gu
This doesn't match
the submitted supplementary agreement
It's a new arrangement for associated companies
Why would a normal adjustment
not notify the guarantor
Why tear off the email precondition
Why after I withdrew
your first reaction wasn't to explain
but to claim I was being emotional
Mr Gu based on the current materials
Su Mingyao's withdrawal of the guarantee
is reasonable risk control
Fu Chenzhou do you know project finance
A little
Mr Fu here is right
From a guarantee perspective withdrawing
an unactivated guarantee intention
is indeed reasonable risk control
Until Gu Group completes the materials
new credit for the West City Yunwan project is suspended
We also need to reassess
the payment milestones
Gu Group please provide within 3 days
an explanation of the associated company's fund usage
Dad I warned you
Whether to investigate the Su family
is your decision
I will investigate